Guide to the United Nations Relief and Rehabilitation Administration records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series VI. Office of the General Counsel
  - Subseries VI.7: Insurance & Claims Division. Country File
    - Belgium Mission, Brussels ECP File General (Box GC/19, Folder Side 2)
    - Canadian Grain Risks (Box GC/19, Folder Side 2)
    - Accidents (Box GC/19, Folder Side 2)
    - China Shipping (Box GC/19, Folder Side 2)
    - Burnett's Case (W.F.) China (Box GC/19, Folder Side 2)
    - Burn's (Paul E.) (Box GC/19, Folder Side 2)
    - Eiden's (R.F.) (Box GC/19, Folder Side 2)
    - Hertzell's (Howard) (Box GC/19, Folder Side 2)
    - Jeep 3332, Ardis M. Huay (Box GC/19, Folder Side 2)
    - Motor and Jeep Jedenov, V. (Box GC/19, Folder Side 2)
    - Moore, Guss N. (Box GC/19, Folder Side 2)
    - Sheehan, H.E. (Box GC/19, Folder Side 2)
    - Talton, J.R. (Box GC/19, Folder Side 2)
    - Todd, O.J. (Box GC/19, Folder Side 2)
    - China F&A Claims (Box GC/19, Folder Side 2)
    - China (Box GC/19, Folder Side 2)
    - Closure: China & Korea General Correspondence (Box GC/19, Folder Side 2)
    - Local Currency (Box GC/19, Folder Side 2)
    - Conversion of Group Life Policies (Box GC/19, Folder Side 2)
    - Survey Hospitals, Reports 304.41 (Box GC/19, Folder Side 2)
    - Insurance and Claims (Box GC/19, Folder Side 2)
    - Incoming Cablegrams (Box GC/19, Folder Side 2)
    - Marine Claims (Box GC/19, Folder Side 2)
    - Pol for China (Box GC/19, Folder Side 2)
    - Proceeds of Sale Reports (Box GC/19, Folder Side 2)
    - Training (Box GC/19, Folder Side 2)
    - DPs Hqs., Paris ECP Correspondence sent Jan. 1- Feb. 28, 1947 (Box GC/19, Folder Side 2)
    - DPs Hqs., Paris ECP Correspondence sent March 1 - April 30, 1047 (Box GC/19, Folder Side 2)
    - DPs Hqs, Paris Correspondence (Box GC/20, Folder Side 1)
    - May 1-31, 1947 (Box GC/20, Folder Side 1)
    - June 1-July 31, 1947 (Box GC/20, Folder Side 1)
    - August 1947 (Box GC/20, Folder Side 1)
    - Reading File (Box GC/20, Folder Side 1)
    - Reading File (Box GC/20, Folder Side 1)
    - Italy Mission, Palermo Incident (Box GC/20, Folder Side 1)
    - Latin American Offices, Closure, General Correspondence Netherlands Mission (Box GC/20, Folder Side 1)
    - South West Pacific Area (Box GC/20, Folder Side 1)
    - UNRRA C.H.Q. Personnel Division ECP Office, Paris (Box GC/20, Folder Side 1)
- Series VII. Office of the Historian
  - Subseries VII.1: Executive Office. Subject File
    - Agreements (2 folders) (Box H/1, Folder Side 1)
    - American Red Cross Relationship with UNRRA (Box H/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Archives Negotiations (Box H/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Authority and Work of the Archivist (Box H/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Area, Bureau of, Organization and Functions (Box H/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Areas, Bureau of, Reports of Operations (Box H/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Audit Subcommittee (Box H/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Brown, Richard, Excerpts from Diary of Trip with Congressmen 21 August - 22 September 1945 (Box H/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Camps, UNRRA (Box H/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Central Files, Suggest Procedures (Box H/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Charts (Box H/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Committees (Box H/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Budget Control (Box H/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Central (Box H/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Closure of UNRRA (3 folders) (Box H/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Committee of Review, Minutes (Box H/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Cooperatives in European Countries (Box H/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Correspondence, Letters from Woodbridge (Box H/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Correspondence, Letters from Woodbridge (Box H/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Correspondence, Woodbridge with Katzin (Box H/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Correspondence from Rosemary Miller (Box H/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Director General's Staff and Personal Meetings, March - August 1944 (Box H/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Director General's Meetings, September 1944 - January 1945 (Box H/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Displaced Persons (3 folders) plus: (Box H/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Bilateral Agreements (Box H/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Burinski Papers (Box H/1, Folder Side 1)
    - DP Division (Box H/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Hoehler File (Box H/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Distribution (Box H/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Finance, Memoranda Concerning Fiscal and Budgetary (Box H/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Food, Emergency Conference on European Cereal Supplies (Box H/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Food and Agricultural Organization (FAO), Summary of Activities Resulting from Use of Funds Transferred by UNRRA (Box H/1, Folder Side 2)
    - General Counsel Monthly Reports (Box H/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Headquarters Files, Disposition of (Box H/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Health Division (Box H/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Historian, Directive to Office of (Box H/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Historian, File Received from Secretariat (Box H/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Historian Office, Personnel and General Expenses of (Box H/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Historical File, UNRRA Miscellaneous Letters and Documents (Box H/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Historical File, Plans for the History of UNRRA (Box H/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Historical Section (Box H/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Authorization of Official History June 1946 (Box H/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Plans for Collection of Records and Letters, 1945 Extra Copies (Box H/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Plans for Collection of Records through May 1946 (Box H/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Progress Reports (Box H/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Records Management, General (Box H/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Relations with Member Governments Covering Records Pertaining to UNRRA (Box H/1, Folder Side 2)
    - History (Box H/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Printing Estimate (Box H/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Proposed Publications re UNRRA (Box H/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Questions for the History of UNRRA (Box H/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Status Reports, History Project (Box H/1, Folder Side 2)
    - History Staff Members, Notes for (Box H/1, Folder Side 2)
    - International Labor Organization (Box H/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Interviews (3 folders) (Box H/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Interviews with Central Committee Members (Box H/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Jews in Nazi Occupied Europe (Box H/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Legislative History of H.J. Res 192 and Amendments Thereto (Box H/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Lehman, Herbert H. (Box H/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Meeting (8), February - December 1944 Staff Meetings (Box H/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Memos - Caustin (Box H/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Military Authorities, Relations with (Box H/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Mission Reports, Review Committee on (Box H/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Monographs, Correspondence re (Box H/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Accounts and Finance (Box H/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Administration (Box H/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Agricultural Rehabilitation (Box H/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Audit Subcommittee (Box H/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Controller, Office of (Box H/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Diplomatic Advisor (Box H/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Director General's Office (Box H/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Displaced Persons (Box H/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Executive Officer, Chief, Office of (Box H/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Finance (Box H/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Financial Advisor's Office (Box H/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Food Division (Box H/1, Folder Side 2)
    - General Counsel (Box H/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Health Division (Box H/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Industrial Rehabilitation (Box H/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Personnel (Box H/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Public Information (Box H/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Secretariat (Box H/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Services, Bureau of (Box H/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Supply Division (Box H/2, Folder Side 1)
    - United Nations (Box H/2, Folder Side 1)
  - Subseries VII.2: Executive Office. Country File
    - Albania (Box H/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Mission (Box H/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Mission History (Box H/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Argentine Office, Reports from (Box H/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Australia (Box H/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Lapstone Conference (Box H/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Mission (Box H/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Austria (Box H/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Nutrition Health in Vienna (Box H/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Balkan (Box H/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Mission (Box H/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Administrative Regulations, Directives (Box H/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Budget (Box H/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Camps Reports (Box H/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Correspondence (Box H/2, Folder Side 2)
    - History (Box H/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Reports (Box H/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Agencies Interested in Balkan Relief Operation (Box H/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Belgian Mission Reports (Box H/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Brazil Procurement and Shipping (Box H/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Byelorussia (Box H/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Canada (Box H/2, Folder Side 2)
    - China (Box H/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Agricultural Rehabilitation (Box H/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Closure Instructions (Box H/2, Folder Side 2)
    - History (Box H/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Plan for China Project (Box H/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Progress Report (Box H/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Reports (Box H/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Czechoslovakia (2 Folders) (Box H/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Denmark (Box H/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Dodecanese (2 Folders) (Box H/3, Folder Side 1)
    - Conference on Program of Operation Overall Budget. All Commodities August 1945 through December 1946 (Box H/3, Folder Side 1)
    - Ethiopia (Box H/3, Folder Side 1)
    - ERO (2 Folders) (Box H/3, Folder Side 1)
    - Administration (Box H/3, Folder Side 1)
    - Administrative Council Minutes (Box H/3, Folder Side 1)
    - Administrative Council Meetings Minutes (Box H/3, Folder Side 1)
    - Administrative Orders (Box H/3, Folder Side 1)
    - Closure, European Field Missions Special Committee on Reorganization Papers (Box H/3, Folder Side 1)
    - Closure Plan (2 Folders) (Box H/3, Folder Side 1)
    - Correspondence (Box H/3, Folder Side 1)
    - Department of Relief Services July 1945 (Box H/3, Folder Side 1)
    - Director General Staff Meeting (Box H/3, Folder Side 1)
    - DPs Weekly Reports (Box H/3, Folder Side 1)
    - Economic and Political Background Reports Notes for Week (Box H/3, Folder Side 1)
    - Monographs (Box H/3, Folder Side 1)
    - Organization (Box H/3, Folder Side 1)
    - Procedures (Box H/3, Folder Side 1)
    - Progress Reports File R/2 (Box H/3, Folder Side 1)
    - Rundown Policy (Box H/3, Folder Side 1)
    - Progress Reports (Box H/3, Folder Side 1)
    - Progress Reports (Box H/3, Folder Side 2)
    - Rundown (Box H/3, Folder Side 2)
    - Supply Closure Committee (Box H/3, Folder Side 2)
    - Telephone Conversations (Box H/3, Folder Side 2)
    - Far East (Box H/3, Folder Side 2)
    - Correspondence to Price, Historical Section Secretarial (Box H/3, Folder Side 2)
    - Closure Instructions (Box H/3, Folder Side 2)
    - DPs (Box H/3, Folder Side 2)
    - Reports of UNRRA Activities (Box H/3, Folder Side 2)
    - UNRRA Activities in and for the Far East Quarterly, 3rd and 4th Quarters 1945, 1946 (Box H/3, Folder Side 2)
    - Preliminary Country Surveys (Box H/3, Folder Side 2)
    - Minutes of Meetings, 26 May 1945 - 20 Feb. 1946 (Box H/3, Folder Side 2)
    - France, Relation with UNRRA (Box H/3, Folder Side 2)
    - Germany (Box H/3, Folder Side 2)
    - Gran Ville and Haaren Bases (Box H/3, Folder Side 2)
    - Greece (Box H/3, Folder Side 2)
    - Memorandum of the Greek Delegation to the UNRRA (Box H/3, Folder Side 2)
    - Reports (Box H/3, Folder Side 2)
    - Budgets (Box H/3, Folder Side 2)
    - Reports (Box H/3, Folder Side 2)
    - India (Box H/4, Folder Side 1)
    - Italy (Box H/4, Folder Side 1)
    - Camps (Box H/4, Folder Side 1)
    - Historical Section (Box H/4, Folder Side 1)
    - Minutes of Property Committee Meeting (Box H/4, Folder Side 1)
    - Monthly Reports (Box H/4, Folder Side 1)
    - Overseas Mission (Box H/4, Folder Side 1)
    - Regional Letters (Box H/4, Folder Side 1)
    - Rome Conference (Box H/4, Folder Side 1)
    - Weekly Letters (Box H/4, Folder Side 1)
    - Coal Requirements (Box H/4, Folder Side 1)
    - Food Position (Box H/4, Folder Side 1)
    - Military Operations (Box H/4, Folder Side 1)
    - Relation with UNRRA (Box H/4, Folder Side 1)
    - Relief to (Box H/4, Folder Side 1)
    - Reports (Box H/4, Folder Side 1)
    - Shipping (Box H/4, Folder Side 1)
    - Monthly Reports (5 folders) (Box H/4, Folder Side 1)
    - Korea, Correspondence re Monographs (Box H/4, Folder Side 1)
    - Latin American Procurement (Box H/4, Folder Side 1)
    - Luxembourg Mission Reports (Box H/4, Folder Side 1)
    - Liaison Office (Box H/4, Folder Side 1)
    - Middle East (Box H/4, Folder Side 2)
    - Netherlands, Relief Assistance (Box H/4, Folder Side 2)
    - New Zealand (Box H/4, Folder Side 2)
    - Norway (Box H/4, Folder Side 2)
    - Philippines (Box H/4, Folder Side 2)
    - Poland (Box H/4, Folder Side 2)
    - Roumania (Box H/4, Folder Side 2)
    - Sweden (Box H/4, Folder Side 2)
    - Switzerland (Box H/4, Folder Side 2)
    - SWPA, Historical Section Secretariat Plans for Collection of Records (Box H/4, Folder Side 2)
    - Ukraine (Box H/4, Folder Side 2)
    - UK (Box H/4, Folder Side 2)
    - Misc. (Box H/4, Folder Side 2)
    - UNRRA Early Plans for (Box H/4, Folder Side 2)
    - USSR (Box H/4, Folder Side 2)
    - Uruguay (Box H/4, Folder Side 2)
    - Venezuela (Box H/4, Folder Side 2)
    - Yugoslavia (Box H/4, Folder Side 2)
    - Mission (Box H/4, Folder Side 2)
    - Monthly Reports (Box H/4, Folder Side 2)
  - Subseries VII.3: Executive Office. Monographs
    - GC 1 Notes on the Development & Functions of the DG's Office (Box H/4, Folder Side 2)
    - GC 2 Agreements on Retention and Transfer of Title (Box H/4, Folder Side 2)
    - GC 3 Agreements with the Govt. of Greece (Box H/4, Folder Side 2)
    - GC 4 Agreements with Czechoslovakia (Box H/4, Folder Side 2)
    - GC 5 Agreement with Yugoslavia (Box H/4, Folder Side 2)
    - GC 6 Agreement with Albania (Box H/4, Folder Side 2)
    - GC 7 First Agreement with Italy (Box H/4, Folder Side 2)
    - GC 8 Supplementary Agreement with Italy (Box H/4, Folder Side 2)
    - GC 9 Agreement with San Marino (Box H/4, Folder Side 2)
    - GC 10 Agreement with the Dedecanese (Box H/4, Folder Side 2)
    - GC 11 Agreement with Byelorussia and the Ukraine (Box H/4, Folder Side 2)
    - GC 12 Agreement with Ethiopia (Box H/4, Folder Side 2)
    - GC 13 Agreement for DP Operations in Germany (Box H/4, Folder Side 2)
    - GC 14 Negotiation of the Arrangements for the Emergency Supply Program (Box H/4, Folder Side 2)
    - GC 15 General Activities of the Office of the General Counsel (Box H/4, Folder Side 2)
    - GC 16 Privileges & Immunities Granted the Administration by Member Govts (Box H/4, Folder Side 2)
    - GC 17 Memo on the Negotiations Leading up to the Execution of the Basic Agreement between the Chinese Government & UNRRA (Box H/4, Folder Side 2)
    - GC 18 Report on Reception of Cargo at European Ports of Discharge, Monograph File by James M. Hastie (Box H/4, Folder Side 2)
    - SE 1 Secretariat Introductory and Overall Statement (Box H/4, Folder Side 2)
    - SE 2 History of UNRRA (Box H/4, Folder Side 2)
    - SE 3 History of the Committee Division (Box H/4, Folder Side 2)
    - SE 4 History of the Reports Division (Box H/4, Folder Side 2)
    - SE 5 Document Office (Box H/4, Folder Side 2)
    - SE 6 History of the Library (Box H/4, Folder Side 2)
    - SE 7 "The UNRRA Council" Appendices (Box H/4, Folder Side 2)
    - SE 7a The UNRRA Appendices (Box H/5, Folder Side 1)
    - SE 8 Structure of UNRRA Committees with Special Reference to Certain Phases of the Activities of the Central Committee and the Committee of the Council for Europe (Box H/5, Folder Side 1)
    - SE 9 Committee on DPs (Box H/5, Folder Side 1)
    - SE 10 The Work of UNRRA by F. Ashton Gwatkin (Box H/5, Folder Side 1)
    - FE 1 A History of the Office of Far Eastern Affairs (through Dec. 31, 1946) (Box H/5, Folder Side 1)
    - PI 1 Public Information (Box H/5, Folder Side 1)
    - DA 1 Historical Sketch on Diplomatic Advisor's Office (Box H/5, Folder Side 1)
    - DA 2 Historical Sketch of Diplomatic Advisor's Office (Box H/5, Folder Side 1)
    - FA 1" "Ability to Pay" Financial Adviser (Box H/5, Folder Side 1)
    - FA 2 Proceed from Sale by Recipient Countries of UNRRA supplies (Box H/5, Folder Side 1)
    - BA 1 The Coordination of Policy and Procedure (Box H/5, Folder Side 1)
    - BA 2 Division of Procedural Coordination (Box H/5, Folder Side 1)
    - BA 3 History of Overseas Administrative Requirement Branch (Box H/5, Folder Side 1)
    - BA 4 Liquidation Planning Program (Box H/5, Folder Side 1)
    - BA 6 Personnel UNRRA Administration; China Office Management (Box H/5, Folder Side 1)
    - BA 7 Hq. Recruitment of Non US Nationals for UNRRA (Box H/5, Folder Side 1)
    - BA 8 Development Personnel Policies (Box H/5, Folder Side 1)
    - BA 9 Personnel "The Training Program" (Box H/5, Folder Side 1)
    - BA 10 Recruitment of a European Mission Personnel Reserve (Box H/5, Folder Side 1)
    - BA 11 Recruitment of US Nationals (Box H/5, Folder Side 1)
    - BA 12 Outplacement (Box H/5, Folder Side 1)
    - BA 13 Returned Field Personnel (Box H/5, Folder Side 1)
    - BA 14 Personnel Administration in OFRRO (Box H/5, Folder Side 1)
    - BA 15 Reporting on Training in Europe (Box H/5, Folder Side 1)
    - BA 16 UNRRA's Personnel Division, Section I (Box H/5, Folder Side 1)
    - BA 16 UNRRA's Personnel Division, Section II (Box H/5, Folder Side 1)
    - BA 17 Fellowships (Box H/5, Folder Side 1)
    - BA 18 Headquarters Recruitment of the Balkan Mission (Box H/5, Folder Side 1)
    - CR 1 History of the Records Section (Box H/5, Folder Side 1)
    - CR 2 History of the Code and Cable Section (Box H/5, Folder Side 1)
    - CR 3 History of the Postal Section (Box H/5, Folder Side 1)
    - CR 4 History to the Telephone Section (Box H/5, Folder Side 1)
    - CR 5 The Story of the international Cable Communications within UNRRA (Box H/5, Folder Side 1)
    - BS Supply 1 Organizational History of the Bureau of Supply (Box H/5, Folder Side 2)
    - BS Supply 2 Notes on the Operational and Policies of the Bureau of Supply (Box H/5, Folder Side 2)
    - BS Supply 3 The Development and Fulfillment of the UNRRA Supply Program (Box H/5, Folder Side 2)
    - BS Supply 4 History of the Committee on Supplies by Addison Brandon (Box H/5, Folder Side 2)
    - BS Supply 5 Committee on Supplies (Box H/5, Folder Side 2)
    - BS Supply 6 Outline of UNRRA Supply Problems (from CS Verbatim Minutes) (Box H/5, Folder Side 2)
    - BS Supply 6a History of the Program Subcommittee of the Central Committee (Box H/5, Folder Side 2)
    - BS Supply 7 Notes on Bureau of Supply Personalities (Box H/5, Folder Side 2)
    - BS Supply 8 Organizational and Policy Relationships between UNRRA and the Combined Boards (Confidential) (Box H/5, Folder Side 2)
    - BS Supply 9 An Analysis of UNRRA, Military Supply Relationships (Box H/5, Folder Side 2)
    - BS Supply 10 Emergency Relief Supplies for Northwest Europe (Box H/5, Folder Side 2)
    - BS Supply 11 Contributed Supplies (Box H/5, Folder Side 2)
    - BS Supply 12 History of the Ocean Shipping Division (Box H/5, Folder Side 2)
    - BS Supply 12a Appendices 1-8 of the History of the Ocean Shipping Division (Box H/5, Folder Side 2)
    - BS Supply 13 History of UNRRA in Canada by Guy Tombs (Box H/5, Folder Side 2)
    - BS Supply 14 History of the Country Programs Division (Box H/5, Folder Side 2)
    - BS Supply 15 The Allocation of UNRRA Supplies, a Study in Decency in International Relations (Box H/5, Folder Side 2)
    - BS Supply 16 Policies and Procedures in the Canadain UNRRA Supply Operation (Box H/5, Folder Side 2)
    - BS Supply 17 The Origin of UNRRA's Supply Program (Box H/5, Folder Side 2)
    - BS Agri 1-la UNRRA's Agricultural Rehabilitation Activities, Vols. I,II (Box H/5, Folder Side 2)
    - BS Agri 2 Water and Land Problems in China (Box H/5, Folder Side 2)
    - BS Agri 3 Historical Monograph, Fisheries Division (Box H/5, Folder Side 2)
    - BS Agri 4 Report on China Fisheries (Box H/5, Folder Side 2)
    - BS Agri 5 UNRRA Livestock Program (Box H/5, Folder Side 2)
    - BS Agri 6 Farm Machinery Procurement and Distribution (Box H/6, Folder Side 1)
    - BS Agri 7 History of Farm Tool Shop Program (Box H/6, Folder Side 1)
    - BS Agri 8 Hand Toos and Repair Materials (Box H/6, Folder Side 1)
    - BS Agri 9 Bags, Bagging and Agricultural Twines (Box H/6, Folder Side 1)
    - BS Agri 10 History of UNRRA Brethren Service Unit in China (Box H/6, Folder Side 1)
    - BS Agri 11 Field Services Branch (Box H/6, Folder Side 1)
    - BS Agri 12 Agricultural Industry Service (Box H/6, Folder Side 1)
    - BS Agri 13 Agricultural Rehabilitation, Country Programs (Box H/6, Folder Side 1)
    - BS Agri 14 Program Analysis Branch (Box H/6, Folder Side 1)
    - BS Agri 15 Surprop Procurement, Agricultural Rehabilitation (Box H/6, Folder Side 1)
    - BS Agri 16 Land Reclamation (Box H/6, Folder Side 1)
    - BS Agri 17 Veterinary Section (Box H/6, Folder Side 1)
    - BS Agri 18 Seeds (Box H/6, Folder Side 1)
    - BS Agri 19 Fertilizer (Box H/6, Folder Side 1)
    - BS Agri 20 Pesticides (Box H/6, Folder Side 1)
    - BS Agri 21 Food Procession (Box H/6, Folder Side 1)
    - BS IR 3 Surplus Procurement for Industrial Rehabilitation (Box H/6, Folder Side 1)
    - BS IR 4 Work of the Standing Technical Committee on Industrial Rehabilitation and the Subcommittee of the Council for Europe (Box H/6, Folder Side 1)
    - BS IR 5 UNRRA's Program of Industrial Rehabilitation Services (Box H/6, Folder Side 1)
    - BS IR 6 Industrial Rehabilitation Services (Box H/6, Folder Side 1)
    - BS IR 8b Tires and Tubes (Box H/6, Folder Side 1)
    - BS IR 8c UNRRA's Program of Industrial Rehabilitation for Automotive Shops (Box H/6, Folder Side 1)
    - BS IR 8d Road Transport Division, Automotive Spare Parts (Box H/6, Folder Side 1)
    - BS IR 9 UNRRA's Program for Railway Transportation Equipment (Box H/6, Folder Side 1)
    - BS IR 9a Australian Locomotive for China (Box H/6, Folder Side 1)
    - BS IR 9a Historical Monograph Rail Transport Equipment Cars & Locomotive (Box H/6, Folder Side 1)
    - BS IR 9b Rails and Ties (Box H/6, Folder Side 1)
    - BS IR lOa Program for Water Transport and Port Rehabilitation China (Box H/6, Folder Side 1)
    - BS IR lOb UNRRA's Program for Water Transport and Port Rehab., Greece, Poland and Yugoslavia (Box H/6, Folder Side 1)
    - BS IR 11 UNRRA Program for Telecommunications (Box H/6, Folder Side 1)
    - BS IR 12 Program for Building Construction Equipment (Box H/6, Folder Side 1)
    - BS IR 13 History of the Fuel Branch (Box H/6, Folder Side 1)
    - BS IR 13a Historical Monograph Coal (Box H/6, Folder Side 1)
    - BS IR 14 Historical Machine Tools Section (Box H/6, Folder Side 1)
    - BS IR 14a History of Machine Repair Program (Box H/6, Folder Side 1)
    - BS IR 15 Program of Public Utilities (Box H/6, Folder Side 1)
    - BS IR 16 Program for Mining (Box H/6, Folder Side 1)
    - BS IR 17 Program for Raw Materials (Box H/6, Folder Side 1)
    - BS IR 18 Misc. Consumers Goods Program (Box H/6, Folder Side 1)
    - BS IR 19 Program for Industrial Relief and Rehab. for Processing Industry (Box H/6, Folder Side 1)
    - BS IR 20 Program for Procurement and Shipping Process (Box H/6, Folder Side 1)
    - BS IR 21 Program for Procurement Control and Reports (Box H/6, Folder Side 1)
    - BS IR 22a Program of Industrial Relief and Rehab. for Albania (Box H/6, Folder Side 1)
    - BS IR 22b Program of Industrial Relief and Rehab. for Austria (Box H/6, Folder Side 1)